[](https://retrospring.net/ "Retrospring")Toggle navigation

Retrospring is shutting down on 1st March, 2025 [Read more](https://blog.retrospring.net/retrospring-is-shutting-down-on-1st-march-2025)

Privacy Policy
==============

This Privacy Policy describes how and when Retrospring uses and collects your data, checks your information and shares with other Services.

Information Collection and Use
------------------------------

#### Basic Account Information

Upon creation of a Retrospring account, some personal information such as your username, password, and email address is collected and stored internally. Asking questions anonymously or browsing any other areas of the service does not require registration or the providing of any further information.

Public information like a short biography, a link to your website, your location or a profile picture can be provided after registration. This information is viewable by any visitor of the site, registered or unregistered, and therefore should not contain any critical information about you or someone else.

#### Answers and Questions

Our Service primarily is designed to ask your friends and other people from around the world questions or answer them. Most of the information you provide us is information you are asking us to make public. This information does not only include the questions, answers, comments and smiles, but also the lists you create, the people you follow and other bits of information that result from using our Service.

#### Cookies

Like many websites, we use cookies and similar technologies to collect additional website usage data and to improve our Services. A cookie is a small data file that is transferred to your computer's hard disk. Retrospring uses persistant cookies to improve the users browsing experience and to to better understand how you interact with our Services. Most Internet browsers automatically accept cookies. You can instruct your browser, by changing its settings, to stop accepting cookies or to prompt you before accepting a cookie from the websites you visit. However, the Services may not function properly if you disable cookies.

#### Non-personal Identification Information

When using our Services, we may receive technical information ("Non-personal Identification") information such as your IP address, browser type, operating system, the referring web page, pages visited, location, search terms, and cookie information. We receive this data when you interact with our Services, for example, when you visit our websites or sign into our Services.

#### Third-Party Services

Retrospring uses a variety of third-party services to help provide our Services or to share your answers to, if connected, other Services like Twitter. These third-party service providers may collect information sent by your browser as part of a web page request, such as cookies or your IP address. Please refer to their Privacy Policies in regard to how they handle your data.

Information Sharing
-------------------

Retrospring will keep any collected data (see "Information Collection and Use" above) encrypted on our servers. Any information shared with other Services is controlled by the user itself, as we only supply sharing to these. If a user isn't satisfied with Terms from another Service they shouldn't connect their accounts or remove access over the Sharing page on the profile settings page.

Notwithstanding anything to the contrary in this Policy, we may preserve or disclose your information if we believe that it is reasonably necessary to comply with a law, regulation or legal request; to protect the safety of any person; to address fraud, security or technical issues; or to protect Retrospring's rights or property. However, nothing in this Privacy Policy is intended to limit any legal defenses or objections that you may have to a third party’s, including a government’s, request to disclose your information.

Modifying Your Personal Information
-----------------------------------

If you are a registered user of our Services, we provide you with tools and account settings to access or modify the personal information you provided to us and associated with your account.

You can also permanently delete your Retrospring account with a button at the bottom of the [account settings page](https://retrospring.net/settings/account). Removing your account will cease your ability to log in with your credentials and the loss of all your data you supplied to the Service.

Our Policy Towards Children
---------------------------

Our Services are not directed to persons under 14. If you become aware that your child has provided us with personal information without your consent, contact us on [\[email protected\]](https://retrospring.net/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) . We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under 14. If we become aware that a child under 14 has provided us with personal information, we take steps to remove such information and terminate the child's account.

Last Revision
-------------

This Privacy Policy was last updated on **December 26nd, 2021**

[_You can view a revision history of this document on GitHub._](https://github.com/Retrospring/retrospring/commits/master/service-docs/en/policy/privacy.md)

Retrospring uses **Markdown** for formatting

`*italic text*` for _italic text_

`**bold text**` for **bold text**

`[link](https://example.com)` for [link](https://example.com/)

##### Keyboard Shortcuts

Close

##### Navigation

* Timeline g t
* Inbox g i
* Notifications g n
* Show profile g p

##### Site-wide

* Move selection up k
* Move selection down j
* Ask a question n
* Load more .
* Show this dialog ?

##### Answer actions

* Smile s
* View comments x
* Write a comment c
* View all answers a
* View answer page l
